

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm a 25 years old Graphic Designer with a passion for Web. I love working in multi-cultural, challenging environments.

After Turkey and Japan, I ended up by the beautiful lake in Lausanne. I'll be staying here for a while, enjoying all the chocolate and the view, oh and working in amazing projects.

DESIGN SKILLS

Software

Adobe Photoshop	••••
Adobe Illustrator	••••
Adobe Indesign	••••
Final Cut Pro	••••
HTML & CSS	••••
Javascript & Jquery	••••
Github	••••

Artistic

Illustration	••••
Grid & Layout	••••
Typography	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
UX/UI	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Image editing	••••

Social

Fast learner Adaptable Creative Communicative Persistent Responsible Open-minded

OTHER AWESOME FACTS ABOUT ME



Feb 2014 - Feb 2015 One Two Triangle

Illustration collaborative project with weekly illustrations throughout the course of a year *onetwotriangle.com*



Jan 2013 - Jul 2014 Berry Duo act

Created performance duo based on story telling, circus and dance. Within a year had a steady schedule and group of followers facebook.com/BerryMagic



August 2013

Cover Illustration for "Kansai Scene" Magazine Illustration and article for n°1 international magazine in Osaka - 15 000 monthly copies rrrita.com/Kansai-Scene

LANGUAGES



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2014 - current UX/UI development notions
Ux/UI Developer Github and team projects
@Tasboa Lda Lisbon, Portugal Ability to keep track of tasks

May - Jun 2014
English Teacher
(conversational classes)
@Kyoto Women's University
Kyoto, Japan

Greater cultural awareness Communication skills Organization Management

Mar 2013 - Mar 2014

Head Teacher (10 year olds)
 Assistant Kindergarten Teacher (1-6 year olds)
 @Minerva/BLKids International Osaka, Japan

Responsability Ability to grab and keep attention Improvisation skills

Oct 2011 - Feb 2013 Graphic/Editorial Designer @Jibun Mirai Associé Osaka, Japan

Ability to work under tight deadlines Attention to detail Sense of esthetics

2010

Freelance Graphich Designer

Monitor of paintball activities

@Emboscada, LDA

Porto, Portugal

Planning activities Time managing skills Customizing services

EDUCATION

2014 - current

Front-End Web Developer Udacity - Nanodegree

2008 - 2011

BA in Communication Design

Project Marketing Design Management

ESAD - Escola Superior de Artes e Design Porto, Portugal

Sep 2009 - Feb 2011

Erasmus Programme - Graphic Design Yildiz Technical University Istanbul, Turkey

HOBBIES & INTERESTS











REFERENCES



João Pedro Sinde M Martino Creative director / Designer Teacher - Project I (bachelor degree)

Teacher - Masters in Graphic Design and Editorial Project

+351 91 886 8681 @Atelier Martino&Jaña @ESAD Superior School of Arts and Design @FBAUP Porto University Fine Arts College



Michiko Matsumoto Sales manager 06 4706 5710 michiko_mt@minel.jp @Minerva English School



Kristen Anne Kuhl Head Teacher +81 80 3832 1421 Kuhlio1421@gmail.com @Abroad International School



Andrew White Head Teacher a27white@hotmail.com @BL-Kids (Minerva)



Nuno Cardoso Lead Designer +81 80 4644 1982 cardosonuno@gmail.com @Jibun Mirai Associé